[
  {
    "question": "Psychology",
    "answer": "An area of science that focuses on people, and in particular, how the mind and feelings may influence behaviors.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "d0653083-961c-4e2f-abae-895f6ae1fab6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Adherence",
    "answer": "The level of commitment to a behavior or plan of action.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "3ea9c4da-7cb2-473e-b5e7-d9976c8b16d5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Motivation",
    "answer": "The intensity and direction of someone’s effort to participate in an activity or engage in a behavior.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "2e687caf-c3a8-4dce-a0c5-16b913df968e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Socioeconomic status",
    "answer": "The social standing of a person or group that includes education, income, and occupation.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "3097507d-1980-443f-bc32-724ac3345466"
  },
  {
    "question": "Amotivation",
    "answer": "Describes when someone is not motivated to engage in an activity or behavior.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "737a1fc0-374f-46cb-b4a9-1645bc719142"
  },
  {
    "question": "Extrinsic motivation",
    "answer": "When someone participates in an activity or behavior for some type of reward or recognition from others.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "70fc869f-5a50-4522-826a-7adf956ad016"
  },
  {
    "question": "Intrinsic motivation",
    "answer": "When people engage in an activity or behavior because they feel a sense of satisfaction or enjoyment",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "a6e9685c-0cd7-4cc8-9386-628731d37189"
  },
  {
    "question": "Outcome goals",
    "answer": "Goals focused on the end result.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "2f763c3f-b44f-441f-8f7d-26d8e23b3c07"
  },
  {
    "question": "Process goals",
    "answer": "Refers to the process of goal pursuit.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "5e93263f-0582-41f1-92fb-a6bb0afa3769"
  },
  {
    "question": "Social support",
    "answer": "The intentional ways that people assist others in achieving a specific behavior.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "eca488fa-aad9-4862-bf43-c5d9af967680"
  },
  {
    "question": "Social physique anxiety",
    "answer": "A specific form of anxiety that occurs in individuals who perceive that others could be negatively evaluating their physique.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "421ebb9b-f13c-47f9-9385-1b572e5e4b8d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ambivalence",
    "answer": "Describes a person’s state of mixed feelings about a situation.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "d85da6c9-0a9e-40b4-b843-ba4888d2a229"
  },
  {
    "question": "Instrumental support",
    "answer": "The actions that directly facilitate a behavior to happen. In the context of exercise, instrumental support can include driving a person to a health club or paying for the gym membership.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "f6971bb1-c35b-4dd9-ab3a-de454f682b6b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Emotional support",
    "answer": "The encouragement and positive reinforcement that is provided from an individual to another, which includes being caring, empathetic, and showing concern.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "1f86b8c4-3fd0-4d82-b12e-9487d981cfb7"
  },
  {
    "question": "Empathy",
    "answer": "The ability to identify with another person’s feelings, attitudes, or thoughts.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "504ce165-3406-4bfd-a867-80058c3be316"
  },
  {
    "question": "Informational support",
    "answer": "Providing accurate, current, and informative information.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "f7f4acac-56a9-48f2-acc4-a29d35d14f91"
  },
  {
    "question": "Companionship support",
    "answer": "When someone engages in a behavior with an individual. This type of support is often observed in an exercise setting where people exercise with a friend or partner.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "650aaa21-26b2-4f59-863c-c6dcfe034fd2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Self-esteem",
    "answer": "The way someone evaluates their own self-worth physically, emotionally, and socially.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "bc3d7348-6fbb-44d3-b847-dac5b5d55ca9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Body image",
    "answer": "The way someone views their physical self or visualizes their body.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "a317fcce-6395-4959-8dbc-b02704188b04"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sleep apnea",
    "answer": "A sleep disorder in which a person’s breathing repeatedly stops and starts, which disrupts the body’s natural sleep cycle.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 3"
    ],
    "id": "bed940df-ac8c-4488-9b4a-e799f919a26c"
  }
]